(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T10:36:57.986337",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
AZKi歌い手企画 LAST V STANDING vol.3
AZKi Singer Project: LAST V STANDING vol.3
本日はあずき対抗企画
Thank you for watching today's Azuki rivalry project,
LAST V STANDING vol.3 をご覧いただきありがとうございます。
"LAST V STANDING vol.3".
開演に先立ちまして、ご来場のお客さまにお願い申し上げます。
Before the show begins, we have a request for all attendees present.
本放送は配信限定のライブとなります。
This broadcast will be a streaming-only live performance.
みなさまそれぞれの環境で近所迷惑にならない程度に応援をお願いいたします。
We ask everyone to cheer in your respective environments so as not to disturb your neighbors.
また、撮影はスクリーンショットのみ可能となります。
Also, photography is only permitted via screenshots.
ぜひライブの様子をハッシュタグ LVS3 で投稿してください。
Please share your live experience using the hashtag #LVS3.
ライブサーフ突然床になるなどの危険行為は禁止となります。
Dangerous acts such as live surfing or suddenly falling to the floor are strictly prohibited.
危険行為により怪我をする可能性もございますので、安全な観覧にご理解ご協力をお願いいたします。
Since dangerous acts may result in injury, we appreciate your understanding and cooperation for safe viewing.
以上です。
That is all.
よくできました。
Job well done.
やめた！よかった！
Yay, we did it!
はい、ということで今日はね
Yes, so today, you know,
なんと2人でやっちゃいますよライブ。
the two of us are actually doing a live stream!
やっちゃいますよ。
We really are!
ついにきちゃいましたよ。
It's finally here!
神宮宮ちゃんと言いつつ
With Miyama-chan and—
あ、ちょっとちょっとじゃあやろうあれ。やろうやろう。
Ah, wait, wait, let's do that huddle. Let's do it.
エンジン組みたいと思います。
We'd like to do a team cheer.
皆さんよろしいでしょうか？
Is everyone ready?
はい、オッケーです！
Yes, okay!
それでは、掛け声はめあずで行きましょうか。
Well then, let's do "Mea-azu" for our chant.
はい。
Okay.
では、お願いします！
Then, ready?
行きますよ。
Here we go.
メア・アズ！メア・アズ！あー！
Mea-azu! Mea-azu! Aaah!
ということで、開演までちょっと待っててね！ 待っててね！
So everyone, please wait a little bit until the show starts! Wait for us!
零れ光る あなた の 声
Your voice echoes and spills forth,
黒い 闇 を 照らす
illuminating the black darkness.
乾い た 空 を 越え て 巡る 記憶 の 色 は 褪せ て 溶け 滲ん だ
Crossing the dry sky, our memories fade and melt away.
冷たく 刻む 時 の 針 が 孤独 の 淵 へ 誘う
The coldly ticking hands of time lead us into the abyss of solitude.
交わし た 想い は 消え ない よ
Our intertwined feelings will never fade away,
誓い 合っ た 未来 で 逢う ため
so that we can meet again in the promised future.
満ち た 波 に 浮かぶ 星 は 遠い 夢 を 映し 燃え て く
The stars floating on the brimming waves reflect a distant dream and burn bright.
僅か 触れ た 指 の 熱 を 蘇ら せる 幻 . . .
Bringing back the warmth of the fingers we barely touched...
逃れ られ ない 運命 で も
Even if trapped in an inescapable destiny,
かけがえの無い 存在 に 救わ れ
we are saved by an irreplaceable existence.
煌めく 風 を 掴む よう に
As if catching the shimmering wind,
崩れる 世界 信じ た 心臓 と 揺れる 瞳 の 奥
I believed in the collapsing world, holding onto my beating heart and trembling eyes.
忘れ ない よ 透明 な 涙
I will never forget those transparent tears.
静寂 に 包ま れ た 藍い 月 祈り を 込める
Enveloped in silence, the pale moon holds my prayers.
ただ ひとつ 不変 の 愛 抱きしめ て 踏み出し た
Embracing a single unchanging love, we stepped forward.
零れ 響く あなた の 声
Your voice echoes,
生きる 意味 を 繋ぐ 温もり
a warmth that connects the meaning of life.
ふたり ここ で 重ね た 日 は
The days we piled up here
永遠 に 輝い て いる . . .
will shine forever...
はい、ということで、改めてまして、こんあずき！
Hi everyone, once again, Kon-Azuki!
こんめお！
Kon-Meo!
はい、今日はですね、あずき待望企画ということで、皆さんお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Yes, today is AZKi's long-awaited event, thank you all for coming!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
では、自己紹介していきましょうか。
Now, let's do our self-introductions.
皆さん、こんあずき！あずきです。今日はめおちゃんとのね、もうね、待ちに待った
Everyone, Kon-Azuki! I'm AZKi. Today is the long-awaited...
待望、楽しみにしてまいりましたので、どうぞ最後までね、最後まで、最後まで見守って欲しい。
...event we've been looking forward to, so please watch us to the very end!
のでよろしくお願いします！いえーい！
Thank you for your support! Yay!
そしてそして、はい！さあ、やってまいりました。世界の名…あはは！
And now it's here, the world's me... haha!
聞けた。台湾ということで、
I heard it. Taiwan, so...
まあ、二人ならではのところとか、あとまあお互いの自分らしい感じみたいなのを思いっきりね届けられたらいいなと思います！
...we can deliver something unique to the two of us, and our own vibe with all our might!
皆さんこの、この立ち姿だけで我ら、いや、すごいシナジー感じるっていうか。
Everyone, just from this standing posture alone, we feel such synergy...
すぐ写真撮っちゃう。そう、すごい赤と青のこの、この二人のコントラストめちゃくちゃ良くないですか？
Taking photos right away! Isn't the contrast between red and blue amazing?
いい！いえーい！ということで、ここからは、はい。どうしますか？
Yes, yay! So, from here on, yes, what should we do?
まあ、そうですね、ここからはソロパート。お！ソロパートありますか？
Well, yes, from here on is the solo parts. Oh, there are solo parts?
ということで、はい。まずはあずきちゃんからお願い……はい、歌っていきたいと思います！ではまずはあずきのアずきのソロからいきたいと思います！それではこの曲から聞いてください、「Creating world」！
So, let's start with AZKi's solo! Please listen to this song, "Creating world"!
この扉の向こうが未開の可能性なら
Beyond this door lies untamed potential,
今を動かせるのかな
so can I set the present in motion?
暗がりを手探りで
Groping through the darkness,
不安と焦燥の中で
amidst anxiety and impatience,
零れた光を見た
I caught a glimpse of spilling light.
手を伸ばして
Reaching out my hand,
この先は君のものだから
because what lies ahead is yours,
時を超えて
transcending time,
繋がるよ、心が今
our hearts connect right now.
創造するの、私のストーリー
Creating my own story,
声を聞かせて、君を知りたいから
let me hear your voice, because I want to know you.
輝かせよう、新しい世界
Let it shine brightly, a brand new world,
生まれた意味を見つけるのさ
finding the very meaning of my birth.
全てが始まる、この場所で
In this place where everything begins,
声が枯れるまで叫んで
I will shout until my voice grows hoarse.
言葉に傷つけられ、悲しみがこぼれるのは弱いからじゃないよ
Hurt by words, if sadness overflows, it's not because you're weak.
勇気はここにあるから、かき消されちゃだめなんだ
Because courage is right here, you mustn't let it be washed away.
君は君のままでいい
It's okay for you to just be yourself.
伝えよ ここぞと 今は
Tell them now, of all times,
共鳴するの 私のストーリー
resonating, my story.
名前を呼んで そばにいるから
Call my name, because I'm right by your side.
音を奏でよう 新しい世界
Let's play music in a new world.
キミに出会う為に 生きていくんだ
I'm living just to meet you.
この場所が 奇跡だから
Because this place is a miracle.
リアルを超えて 繋ぐよ
Transcending reality, I'll connect us.
夜は深く 眠りに落ちて やがて 光が 世界を照らすよ
The night falls deep into sleep, and soon light will illuminate the world.
キミと出逢えたこと 意味を見つけたのさ 共にはい上がって 生きたい
Finding meaning in meeting you, I want to claw my way up together and live.
創造するの 私のストーリー
Creating, my story.
声を聞かせて キミを知りたいから
Let me hear your voice, because I want to know you.
開拓するの 新しい世界
Pioneering a new world.
嘘じゃないんだ キミとのストーリー
It's no lie, my story with you.
全てが始まる この場所で
In this place where everything begins.
歌を歌い続けるよ
I will keep on singing songs.
命の最後の日 奏でる最後の歌 のことを考えてる 知らないうちに
On the last day of life, playing the last song, thinking about it without realizing.
息継ぐ空気みたいに いやむしろ呪いみたいに 歪なほど、かけがえなくそこにある
Like the air I breathe, or rather like a curse, so distorted yet irreplaceable, it's right there.
そう、息が止まるその瞬間まで このミュージックに浸っていたいの “take me” 音の世界じゃこの身体はきっと 溺れてたいの
Until breath stops, I want to be immersed in this music. "Take me," in a soundless world this body surely wants to drown in.
“Take me”
“Eternity” ほんの少しだって生き出しちゃいられない だから
“Eternity,” I couldn't live even a little bit without it, so...
“Take me to heaven” 連れていって あのメロディが私を oh oh
“Take me to heaven,” take me away, that melody pulling me—oh oh
“Eternity” まるで 永遠みたいな 音色で呼ぶ方へ どうか
“Eternity,” calling out in a tone like eternity, please...
“Take me to heaven”
一人で夜を越す日 信じる相手もいない どうしようもないくらい長い夜に
On nights spent alone, with no one to believe in, in such hopelessly long nights,
遺書みたいなプレイリスト 天国向けいつも投げ出している 決して無くさぬように
a playlist like a final note, always tossed toward heaven so as never to lose it.
私の最後の日 抱える最初の答え はきっとまだ胸の中、心臓のように
On my last day, the first answer I hold is surely still inside my chest, like a heartbeat.
息継ぐ空気みたいに いやむしろ呪いみたいに 歪なほど、かけがえなくそこにある
Like the air I breathe, or rather like a curse, so distorted yet irreplaceable, it's right there.
もう何も他に望まない と誓って 一つだけ願いが叶うなら
Vowing to wish for nothing else, if just one wish could come true,
息が止まるその日には
on the day my breath stops...
命の最後の日 奏でる最後の歌
On the final day of life, playing the final song...
のことを考えている 知らないうちに
I'm thinking about it, before I even knew it.
息継ぐ 空気みたいに いわば呪いみたいに
Like air to catch my breath, almost like a curse,
歪な程、かけがえなく そこにある
as distorted as it is irreplaceable, it's right there.
そう、息が止まる その瞬間まで この音楽に浸れていたいの
Yes, until the very moment my breath stops, I want to be immersed in this music.
“Take me” 音のない世界じゃ この体はきっと
"Take me" - in a world without sound, this body surely...
“Eternity” ほんの少しだって 生き出しちゃいられない
"Eternity" - couldn't even survive for just a little while,
だから oh oh
that's why, oh oh.
“Take me to heaven” 連れていって あのメロディで 私を oh oh
"Take me to heaven," lead me away with that melody, take me, oh oh.
“Eternity” たとえ無限の孤独のただ中だとしても
"Eternity" - even if I'm right in the middle of infinite solitude,
だとしても
even so...
“Stairway to Heaven” それでいいの
"Stairway to Heaven," that's fine by me.
“Take me to heaven”
"Take me to heaven"
それでいいの、“Take me to heaven”
That's fine by me, "Take me to heaven."
“Take me” 音のない世界じゃ この体はきっと
"Take me" - in a world without sound, this body surely...
“Eternity” ほんの少しだって 生き出しちゃいられない だから
"Eternity" - couldn't even survive for just a little while, that's why...
“Take me to heaven” 連れていって あのメロディで 私を
"Take me to heaven," lead me away with that melody, take me...
“Stairway to heaven” それでいいの
"Stairway to heaven," that's fine by me.
“Take me to heaven” それでいいの “Take me to heaven”
"Take me to heaven," that's fine by me, "Take me to heaven."
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ということで2曲続けてお送りしました クリエイティングワールド テイクミートゥーヘブン でした！
With that, we've delivered two songs in a row: "Creating World" and "Take me to heaven"!
いかがでしたか？ お水飲んでもいいですか？ (笑)
How was it? Is it alright if I have some water? (Laughs)
ライブお決まり事 お水を飲む
It's the concert tradition: drinking water.
お水飲みました！お水ありがとう！みんなお水、お水スタンプありがとね！
I drank water! Thanks for the water! Everyone, thanks for the water stamps!
すごい、すごい大量のお水が溢れんばかりにありがとうございます。お水助かる。お水助かります。ありがとうございます。700円ありがとうございます。
Wow, thank you so much for the overflowing amount of water. Water is a lifesaver. Water really helps. Thank you!
はい、ということでですね、この感じでどんどん行きたいと思うんですけれども、ここからはですね、まあちょっと、AZKiのちょっと可愛い、可愛い感じのAZKiを、ちょっと…溺れるほどのお水、ありがとうございます！えっと、可愛い感じのAZKiを見せていきたいと思います！
Right, so with that feeling, I'd like to keep going, but from here on... well, AZKi's cute, somewhat cute side—wait, thanks for the water enough to drown in! Um, I want to show you a cute AZKi!
ということで、この曲聞いてください、「リアルメランコリー」！
With that, please listen to this song: "Real Melancholy"!
答えを教えて より夜更けメルランコリー
Tell me the answer, a late-night melancholy.
みんなで！ イェーイ！
Everyone together! Yay!
体の感情が交差する ただしい自分をなにに
My bodily emotions intersect—what am I basing my true self on?
ニトサンを凌いで交差する 世界は一つじゃない
Surpassing two or three, intersecting, the world isn't just one.
いねグットファボの数字増えていく
Likes, goods, and favorite numbers keep increasing.
まん丸にセロファンかざして 首を締める 私の生きる世界は
Holding a cellophane over a full circle, tightening my neck—the world I live in...
自分の手で選ばせてよ
Let me choose it with my own hands!
真夜中のメランコリー 生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
Midnight melancholy, a reborn identity.
好みがこのへんなんだよ
My tastes are kind of weird like this!
上っ面だけのヒストリー
A superficial history...
私は 私は
Am I... am I...
誰かにとって 壊れるの？
breaking for someone else?
理想と現実が交差する
Where reality and ideals intersect,
正しい率はどこ？
where is the right me?
再生回数が落ちていく
Play counts are dropping;
世界はどこも同じだ
the world is the same everywhere.
キャラ属性カテゴライズされていく
Being categorized by character attributes—
誰かに決め付けられた流行りは嫌だな
I hate trends forced upon me by others.
私のやりたいことは
What I want to do...
自分の手で決めさせてよ
let me decide with my own hands!
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight melancholy,
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
a reborn identity.
この波が このへんが 痛いよ
This wave, right here, hurts so much.
分かんないこの想い
I don't understand this feeling,
同じじゃない つまる想い
it's not the same, this clogged feeling.
私は 私は 誰かにとって
Am I... am I for someone...
壊れるの？
breaking?
流行りも好きも どっちも欲しい
Trends and what I love—I want both.
矛盾の文字を 繰り返していく
Repeating words of contradiction.
何番目のコピーじゃないの
I'm not just copy number whatever!
永遠の夜を超えていく 見知らぬ世界へ
Crossing an eternal night to an unfamiliar world.
ひとりめの手を繋いで
Holding hands with the first me...
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight melancholy,
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
a reborn identity.
好みが このへんが 痛いよ
This preference, right here, hurts so much.
分かんない この想い
I don't understand this feeling—
どこかの世界の君へ
to you in some world,
私と似る気持ちの君へ エールを送るよ
to you with feelings like mine, I send my cheering.
真夜中のメランコリー
Midnight melancholy,
生まれ変わるアイデンティティ
a reborn identity.
好みが このへんが 痛いけど
Even though this preference right here hurts,
どこかの世界の君へ
to you in some world,
私と似る気持ちの君へ エールを送るよ
to you with feelings like mine, I send my cheering—
君と私のために
for you and for me.
どうして気付いてしまったの
Why did I have to realize it?
熱くなるほどに 隠しきれない 戸惑い
Confusion I can't hide no matter how passionate I get.
微妙な距離 およそやらな姿勢
A delicate distance, a half-hearted posture—
揺れる心割れないように
so my wavering heart doesn't break.
愛おしい響く胸の鼓動
An endearing, echoing beat in my chest.
呼吸さえままならないのに
Even breathing is beyond me,
きっとどこかで願っているんだ 終わりのない時間を
yet surely I'm wishing somewhere for endless time.
恋の始まりは誰も知らない 私だけの宝物
The start of love is known by no one—a treasure only mine.
少しでも言葉何かにしたら
If I turn it into words, even a little,
飛沫のような笑顔 ぐしゃぶりの泣き顔も全部無くしてしまいそうで
it feels like I'd lose smiles like splashing spray and weeping faces entirely.
もしもひとつだけ叶うんならば
If only one wish could come true,
ただ君のすぐ隣で 過ぎてゆく季節を眺めていたい
I'd want to watch the passing seasons right by your side.
溢れそうな想いは 胸の奥にしまい込んだ
Overflowing feelings tucked deep in my chest—
ふたりの声は空に 吸い込まれてく
our voices are sucked into the sky.
隠した方の左目に どんな僕を映し出すの
What kind of me are you reflecting in your hidden left eye?
開けた方の右目だけじゃ 本当の僕は見えないでしょ
With only your open right eye, you can't see the real me, can you?
シリョクケンサ 二重線の僕が 悪戯に微笑むの
Visual inspection. A double-lined me smiles mischievously.
忘れないで 君の中に 偽物の僕がいる
Don't forget, there is a fake me inside of you.
指示して教えてよ 君の目には見えてるんでしょ
Point and tell me, you can see it with your eyes, can't you?
僕の心の隙間が ぼやけて見えるのならば
If the gaps in my heart appear blurred,
目を閉じて構わないから 君が思うままに
You don't need to close your eyes, just as you wish.
正しく僕を愛せるように 君の目を矯正したくて
Wanting to correct your eyes so you can love me correctly,
使い古したその眼鏡じゃ 本当の僕は見えないでしょ
With those worn-out glasses, you can't see the real me, can you?
シリョクケンサ 消えかけの僕が 悲しげに微笑むの
Visual inspection. A fading me smiles sadly.
忘れないで 君の中に ほんとうの僕がいる
Don't forget, there is a real me inside of you.
目に映るものだけを 信じることしかできない
I can only believe in what is reflected in my eyes,
僕も君も同じだ
You and I are the same.
だからこそ今だけは その心に焼き付けてよ
That's why, only for now, burn it into your heart—
君が知らない僕を
The me you don't know.
少しずつ見えなくなった あの頃は見えた景色
Little by little, the scenery I used to see became invisible.
変わったのは君の方か それとも自分の方か
Did you change, or did I?
指示して教えてよ 君の目には見えてるんでしょ
Point and tell me, you can see it with your eyes, can't you?
僕の心の隙間が ぼやけて見えるのならば
If the gaps in my heart appear blurred,
この胸に手を当て 君に伝えるから
Place your hand on this chest, I will convey it to you—
ほんとうの僕を
The real me.
いつか大人になってしまうのならば
If we someday grow up to be adults,
誰よりもただ二人で 振り向いた先で笑っててほしい
more than anyone, I want the two of us to keep smiling as we look back.
どこまでも募る想いが いつまでもここに在るんだ
The feelings growing endlessly will always be here,
二人の声は空に 溶けてしまう
Our two voices will melt into the sky.
恋の始まりは誰も知らない
Nobody knows the beginning of love,
私だけの宝物を 少しでも言葉なんかにしたくなくて
Reluctant to put my own treasure into words, even a little,
緋弾まりのような笑顔も どしゃぶりの泣き顔も全部
Even the blushing smile, even the downpour of tears,
なくしてしまいそうで
as if I'm about to lose them all...
もしもし一つだけ叶うのならば
If even one wish could come true,
ただ君のすぐ隣で 過ぎていく季節眺めていたい
I just want to watch the passing seasons right by your side.
呆れそうなほどの想いが 胸の奥にしまい込んだ
Feelings almost too absurd, locked deep in my chest,
二人の声は空に 溶けてしまう
Our two voices will melt into the sky.
呆れそうなほどの想いが 胸の奥にしまい込んだ
Feelings almost too absurd, locked deep in my chest,
二人の声は空に 溶けてしまう
Our two voices will melt into the sky,
吸い込まれてく
getting swallowed up.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
はーい、いっぱいハートと拍手ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for all the hearts and applause!
見えてますよ、見えてますよ！
I can see them, I can see them!
はい、ということで、お水も飲みます。
Yes, so, I'm going to have some water.
お水飲んでね。
Drinking water, you know.
あずきのソロパートもいよいよラスト2曲となっております。
AZKi's solo part is finally down to the last two songs.
皆さんまだまだ、まだまだ盛り上がっていけますか？
Everyone, can you still keep getting more and more hyped?
水たっぷりありがとうね。
Thanks so much for the water.
まだまだ盛り上がっていけますか？
Can you still keep getting hyped?
声援と！
Cheers!
ちょっと、ちょっと時差があるけど、いえーい！
There's a bit of a time lag, but yay!
じゃあね、みんなにもね、歌ってもらいたいと思います。
Now, I'd like everyone to sing along too.
みんなウォウォウォして、笑いたいなと思います。
I want us all to 'woah-woah-woah' and smile together.
ということで、次はこの曲、発光体ソーラーサイクル！
And so, next song is—"Hakkoutai Solar Cycle"!
明日を照らすよ sunshine
Illuminating tomorrow, sunshine,
窓から射し込む...扉開いて
streaming through the window... opening the door.
壊してなくなった壁は
The wall that was broken and gone,
いつかあったことも忘れて
forgetting it was ever even there,
壊すためのその拳は 何を作るの
that fist meant for destroying, what is it making?
離れた星の住人が わけも知らず
The inhabitants of a distant star, without knowing why,
またぶつかり合っている
are colliding with each other once again.
ステージのバックライトは 背中に感じるだけじゃない
The stage's backlight isn't just something felt on the back,
次に立つ誰かのために 輝いている
it's shining for whoever stands next.
今すぐ世界は 変わらないけど
The world won't change right away, but
11年後の君に歌うよ
I'll sing to you 11 years from now.
今日も夜空は こんなに冷たいのに
Even though tonight's night sky is so cold,
この街の灯は いつも熱い
this city's lights are always warm.
一人一人のストーリーが あふれているから
Because each and every person's story overflows.
あふれているから
Because it's overflowing,
だから
so
飛び出せ Say Hello!
jump out and say hello!
届け未来的大ショウタイム
Reach out to the future, a grand Showtime!
自信持って もっと激しく遊べ
Have confidence and play harder and wilder!
My sister 今もセーガクジ
My sister, even now as students,
全部叶えていこうよ
let's make all our dreams come true!
夢見る力が地上の星を照らせば
If the power of dreaming illuminates the stars on earth,
誰かの好きが繋がって So Miracle
someone's passions connect—so miraculous.
またいつか花開くよ そらサイコー
Someday flowers will bloom again, sky high!
ぼくら自分と世界の時間を今5月で
Counting down the time for ourselves and the world this May,
世界が大人になってると勘違いして
we mistook it for the world growing up.
あるときーループから放り出されて
Then suddenly thrown out of the loop,
変わり映えしない日々に戸惑う
we're bewildered by unchanging days.
誰かの夢が連鎖してゆくのは
Someone's dream chaining onward—
自由を縛る鎖じゃなくて
it's not a chain binding our freedom,
少しずつでもまだ見ぬ世界
even if just a little, a world yet unseen
見えてたらいいよね
if we could see it, wouldn't that be nice?
飛び出せ Say Hello!
Jump out and say hello!
響け宇宙的Big Wave!
Resonate, cosmic Big Wave!
瞳輝かせた君が好きさ My sister
I love you with your sparkling eyes, my sister.
今もセイガジ いつも全身全霊で
Even now as students, always with all our might,
磁力線の向こう側目指して
aiming for the other side of the magnetic field,
一瞬の閃光が永遠のステージで
a momentary flash on an eternal stage
この世界を変えてくよ そらサイコー
will change this world, sky high!
懐かしいことが心地いいとき
When nostalgic things feel comforting,
新しいことは辛いこと
new things feel difficult.
それでも
Even so,
新しい明日が見たい
I want to see a new tomorrow.
飛び出せ Say Hello!
Jump out and say hello!
届け未来的大ショウタイム
Reach out to the future, a grand Showtime!
自信持って もっと激しく遊べ My sister
Have confidence and play harder and wilder, my sister!
今もセーガジ 全部叶えていこうよ
Even now as students, let's make it all come true!
夢見る力が地上の星を照らせば
If the power of dreaming illuminates the stars on earth,
誰かの好きが繋がって So Miracle
someone's passions connect—so miraculous.
またいつか花開くよ そらサイコー
Someday flowers will bloom again, sky high!
僕らの今が君を動かして
Our present moment moves you,
またいつか花開くよ そらサイコー
and someday flowers will bloom again, sky high!
がんばってだめだって 落ち込んだ日もあるでしょう
Even on days when you tried your best and failed,
ほら 探しに行こう シェケナベイベー☆
come on, let's go search for it, shake it baby☆
いつだって 今だって みんながくれた希望は
Always, right now, the hope everyone gave us
意地っ張りな僕を変えてくれた
changed my stubborn self.
部屋の隅でかかえてた 伝えたい歌とギターのように
Like the song and guitar I held in the corner of my room,
空に浮かぶあの願いは 世界動かす秘めた誓い
that wish floating in the sky is a hidden vow that moves the world.
ありがとう 走りだした 夢をのせ 坂をこえて
Thank you, I started running, carrying my dreams over the hill,
信じ合えるさ 迷わない！ そう思っていた
believing in each other, no hesitation! That's what I thought.
君を照らす光になると信じて ありがとう これからだよ
Believing I'll become the light that shines on you, thank you, from now on.
走り出した
Running forward,
夢をのせて
carrying our dreams,
坂を越えて
climbing over the hills,
信じ合えるさ
we can believe in each other.
迷わない！そう思っていた
I thought I'd never hesitate!
君を照らす 光になると信じて
Believing I'd become a light to shine on you,
ありがとう
Thank you.
これからだよ
This is just the beginning,
つれてくから
I'll take you along
夢の先へ
to the beyond of our dreams.
君がいるなら
With you by my side,
叶わないはずないよなんてね
nothing is impossible, or so I thought.
調子のっちゃって
Getting a little carried away
もいいよね
is fine, right?
いつだって今だって この背中を押したのは
Whenever and wherever, what pushed my back forward
空で笑いかけてくれた君だ
was you, smiling up at the sky.
これからも泣きたくなるような日は来る
Even from now on, there will be days I want to cry,
そんなものは振り払って
but I'll shake those feelings off
待ち合わせはして見よう
and let's make a promise to meet again.
どこまでだって行けるよ
We can go anywhere at all!
わかんない、このままでいいの？
I don't know, is this okay as it is?
わかんない、抱きしめて
I don't know, hold me tight,
生まれたままの素足で育ってよ
grow up with your bare feet just as you were born.
抱いていた あの場所には 僕ではない
In that place I once embraced, it wasn't me...
誰かがいた にじんだ先に 見えた光を待っていた
...someone else was there, waiting for the light that blurred in the distance.
弱虫の ひとりじめした奇跡
A miracle selfishly claimed by a coward—
ありがとう
Thank you.
走り出した
Running forward,
夢をのせて
carrying our dreams,
坂を越えて
climbing over the hills,
信じ合えるさ
we can believe in each other.
迷わない！そう思っていた
I thought I'd never hesitate!
君を照らす 光になると信じて
Believing I'd become a light to shine on you,
ありがとう
Thank you.
君がいるなら
With you by my side,
叶わないはずないよなんてね
nothing is impossible, or so I thought.
調子のっちゃって
Getting a little carried away
もいいよね
is fine, right?
調子のっちゃっていいよね
Getting carried away is fine, right?
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ということでね、めあちゃんのオリジナル曲「ドリームトリッパー」歌わせていただきました！
So, we just sang Mei-chan's original song "Dream Tripper"!
ということは、ということは、ここでめあちゃんを読み込みたいと思います！みんな良いですか？
That means... that means we want to bring Mei-chan on stage right now! Is everyone ready?
みんなコメントの、コメントの準備できてますか？「めあちゃん」で呼びたいと思いますよ。
Are you all ready with your comments? Let's call her out with "Mea-chan"!
はーい！
Ready!
いきますよ！せーの！めあちゃーん！
Here we go! Ready, set! Mea-chan!
はーい！めあだよー！
Hiiii! It's Mea!
めあだよー！めあだよー！
It's Mea! It's Mea!
はい、ということでめあちゃんに再び登場していただきました！
Yes, so we have Mea-chan joining us again on stage!
お疲れ様！
Good job!
ありがとう！いや、めっっちゃよかった！
Thank you! Man, that was amazing!
なんかすごいね、袖にね、めあちゃんが見えて、ちょっとチラチラ出してたりさ。
I could see Mea-chan in the wings, peeking out a little.
なんか一緒に盛り上がって
We were getting hyped together—
そうそう！なんかすごい、こうやってノリノリで、嬉しすぎて、聞いてくれてた！ありがとう！
Yeah! We were getting super into it, I was so happy you were listening! Thank you!
ありがとうございます！ということでここからはね、めあちゃん
Thank you very much! So from here on, Mea-chan...
はい！めあちゃんバトンタッチして
Yes! Passing the baton to Mea-chan,
もうみんなね、もうね、力強いめあちゃんのこのターン、全力でね、盛り上がって行きたいと思います！
everyone, let's get fully hyped for Mea-chan's powerful turn with all our might!
ちょっと、また、また初めから見たい！いや、盛り上げて！盛り上げ隊長！
Wait, I want to watch it from the start again! No, get hyped! Hype leader!
はい、じゃあめあちゃん意気込みどうですか？
Right, so Mea-chan, how are you feeling?
いやー、まあね、あの、AZKi先生から…
Well, you know, from AZKi-sensei...
ちょっと待ってちょっと待って何ですか？
Wait, wait, what is it?
何ですか？
What?
あずきちゃんじゃないの？
Isn't it Azuki-chan?
いや、AZKiせん、あれ？AZKi先生！AZKi先生にするよみんな！
Wait, AZKi-sen... Huh? AZKi-sensei! Let's call her AZKi-sensei, everyone!
ちょっと待ってちょっと待って！ちょっと待ってちょっと待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
何々？
What, what?
はいはい。
Yes, yes.
あ、AZKi先生からね、たくさん、今、なんて言うんだろ、元気もらったので、
Ah, since I got so much energy from AZKi-sensei just now,
そう、パワーもらったので、もう上乗せして、うん、
Yeah, I got her power, so I'll add even more to it,
次のね、自分のターンも飛ばしていきたいと思います！
and keep flying through my turn too!
もう最後まで見るしかない！見てくれ！
You gotta watch till the very end! Check it out!
はい、じゃあ！
Alright, then!
みあちゃんがんばってね！
M-chan, do your best!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、えー、やっぱAZKiちゃんのね、ドリームトリップ、めちゃくちゃ良かった。
Yeah, AZKi-chan's Dream Trip was amazing.
いや、本当にね、歌ってくれてありがとう！AZKi先生！
Seriously, thank you so much for singing, AZKi-sensei!
はい、ここからはみあのターンということで、皆さんまだまだ盛り上がれますか？
Okay, from here on it's Mia's turn. Can everyone still get hyped?
まだまだいけますか？
Can you still keep going?
ありがとう！めっっちゃきれい！コメントもね、ちゃんと見えてます。
Thank you! It's so pretty! I can see your comments loud and clear.
今日は私たちとみんなだけの特別な日です。
Today is a special day just for us and everyone.
私たちだけ、みんなだけじゃなくて、私たちとみんなで一緒に最高の思い出を作ろうね！
Not just us, not just everyone, but together let's make the best memories!
オッケー！
Okay!
よし、それじゃあ、
Alright, then...
早速1曲目歌いたいと思います！
I'd like to perform our first song!
聞いてください、「グラウンド・ゼロ」。
Please listen to "GROUND-ZERO".
解き放て世界へ！
Unleash it to the world!
途切れない闇をゆく
Going through the endless darkness,
希望の火が消えたら その瞬間が行き止まり
If the fire of hope goes out, that moment is a dead end.
思い描いたなにもかも
Whatever you imagined,
その目で確かめるために あの壁を打ち砕け
Break down that wall to verify it with your own eyes.
blow up!
hurry up!
why don't you restart now? 全身と全霊で
Why don't you restart now with body and soul?
knock out! hit it back!
確定も不確定も抱えたままで
Holding both certainty and uncertainty.
目指す場所はひとつだけ
The place I aim for is just one.
hope you take me out
走りだせ
Start running!
この手を伸ばせば 夢に届くかな
If I stretch out this hand, will it reach my dream?
(crossing the world)
胸に刻んだ 今がグラウンド・ゼロ
The present etched in my chest is Ground Zero.
焦げ付くほどに 勇気を燃やして
Burning my courage until it scorches,
(my little wish)
流星に重なる 軌跡描くよ
Drawing a trajectory overlapping with shooting stars.
向かい風に傷ついても
Even if I get hurt by headwinds,
止まらずに進め！
Advance without stopping!
hey! are you ready?
let's get ready to break the wall! come on!
five. four. three. two. one.
explosion!
未来予感した あの場所から私のブレイクは壊れていた
From that place where I sensed the future, my break was broken.
クレシェンドが止まらない 振り返らない！
The crescendo won't stop, I won't look back!
can you set me free?
解き放て
Unleash it!
流した涙のカケラ握りしめ
Clutching the fragments of spilled tears,
(awaken me)
駆け抜けてゆく 答えなんて知らないまま
Running through without even knowing the answer.
信じることを恐れたとしても
Even if I feared believing,
(from my slumber)
秘めた決意はだって抑えきれないから
Because my hidden determination can't be held back.
破裂しそうな想いだけが
Only feelings that feel like they'll burst
揺るぎない真実
Are the unwavering truth.
もっとずっと遠くへ
Further and further away,
銀河さえ超えて 未来まで
Crossing even galaxies, up to the future.
この物語に最高の終末を
Giving this story its ultimate ending,
願い届けるために すべてをささげよう
I'll dedicate everything to making this wish come true.
(崩れ去る前に)
(Before it crumbles away)
この手を伸ばせば 夢に届くかな
If I stretch out this hand, will it reach my dream?
(crossing the world)
胸に刻んだ 今がグラウンド・ゼロ
The present etched in my chest is Ground Zero.
焦げ付くほどに 勇気を燃やして
Burning my courage until it scorches,
(my little wish)
流星に重なる 軌跡描くよ
Drawing a trajectory overlapping with shooting stars.
向かい風に傷ついても
Even if I get hurt by headwinds,
止まらずに進んで
Advancing without stopping.
解き放て世界へ！
Unleash it to the world!
途切れない闇をゆく
Going through the endless darkness,
希望の火が消えたら その瞬間が行き止まり
If the fire of hope goes out, that moment is a dead end.
思い描いたなにもかも その目で確かめるために
Whatever you imagined, verify it with your own eyes
あの壁を打ち砕け
To break down that wall.
揺るぎない真実
Are the unwavering truth.
もっとずっと遠くへ
Further and further away,
銀河さえ超えて 未来まで
Crossing even galaxies, up to the future.
この物語に最高の終末を
Giving this story its ultimate ending,
願い届けるために すべてをささげよう
I'll dedicate everything to making this wish come true.
(崩れ去る前に)
(Before it crumbles away)
この手を伸ばせば 夢に届くかな
If I stretch out this hand, will it reach my dream?
胸に刻んだ 今がグラウンド・ゼロ
The present etched in my chest is Ground Zero.
焦げ付くほどに 勇気を燃やして
Burning my courage until it scorches,
流星に重なる 軌跡描くよ
Drawing a trajectory overlapping with shooting stars.
向かい風に傷ついても
Even if I get hurt by headwinds...
止まらずに進んで...
Moving forward without stopping...
突き放して世界へ
Launching out into the world
サマー☆フロート
Summer Float
もっと汗かきたいじゃないの？
Don't you want to sweat more?
もっと暴れたいじゃないの？
Don't you want to go wild more?
サマー☆フロート、カモン！
Summer Float, come on!
絡まって弾けた光サマデイズ
Summer days of light tangled and bursting,
高く飛行機雲が
vapor trails high above
きらめく空を描いた
drawing a sparkling sky.
高鳴る胸のその理由は
The reason for this pounding heart
寄せては返す波のように伝えられないんだ
is like waves crashing and receding—I just can't say it.
重ねた言葉は二人で笑い合って溶ける
The words we shared melt as we laugh together,
心夏の魔法にかかったみたい
feeling like we've fallen under a midsummer magic spell.
今 Take off, take off 空へ
Now take off, take off into the sky,
飛び出していこう Take off, take off 風を
let's fly out, take off, take off into the wind.
その手と手を合わせて 駆け出す夏の中を
Joining our hands together, running through the summer.
今 Take off, take off 空を
Now take off, take off across the sky,
乗せて行こう Take off, take off 君と
let's carry it on, take off, take off with you.
その手と手を繋いだら
If we connect our hands,
おもいっきり鳴り止まないメロディ
an unstoppable, echoing melody!
眩しい背中に隠す笑顔隠しきれずに
Unable to hide the smile on that dazzling back,
背中を押す南風 いたずらに服を揺らした
the southern wind pushing our backs playfully ruffled our clothes.
この夏にピリオド打つのほりき いつまで経っても
Putting a period to this summer... no matter how long passes,
落ち着かないんだ
I just can't settle down.
重ねた身体は二人でふざけ合って溶ける
The bodies we pressed together melt as we joke around,
目線夏のリズムに溺れていたい
wanting to drown in the rhythm of midsummer eyes.
今 Take off, take off 空へ
Now take off, take off into the sky,
飛び出していこう Take off, take off 風を
let's fly out, take off, take off into the wind.
その手と手を合わせて 駆け出す夏の中を
Joining our hands together, running through the summer.
今 Take off, take off 空を
Now take off, take off across the sky,
乗せて行こう Take off, take off 君と
let's carry it on, take off, take off with you.
その手と手を離したら目を閉じたら
If we let go of our hands and close our eyes...
振り返る影は 遠く影のようになって
The shadow looking back becomes a distant silhouette,
揺らいで結ばれてく 突き上がりの下で
swaying and binding beneath the thrusting lights.
夜に溶けてこのまま 二人で
Melting into the night just like this, the two of us...
今 Take off, take off 空へ
Now take off, take off into the sky,
飛び出していこう Take off, take off 風を
let's fly out, take off, take off into the wind.
その手と手を合わせて 駆け出す夏の中を
Joining our hands together, running through the summer.
今 Take off, take off 空を
Now take off, take off across the sky,
乗せて行こう Take off, take off 君と
let's carry it on, take off, take off with you.
その手と手を繋いだら 終わらない夏祭り
If we connect our hands, an endless summer festival's...
おもいっきり鳴り止まないメロディ
unstoppable, echoing melody!
走れ！
Run!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
2曲続けて聴いていただきました、
You've listened to two songs in a row:
グランドゼロとサマーフロートでした！
"Ground Zero" and "Summer Float."
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
みんな拍手もありがとうございます！
Thank you all for the applause!
じゃあね、次は水を飲みたいと思います。あー、
Now I'm going to drink some water. Ah...
失った水分をここで取り戻すんだ。
I'm going to replenish the moisture I lost here.
ふう、美味しい！
Phew! Delicious!
あ、すごいすごいすごい！
Ah, it's amazing, amazing, amazing!
さっきまで見てたけどね、みんな水分が凄いのよ。
Earlier, while I was watching, everyone's water was amazing!
あー、もうすごいすごいもうね、あのこの会場がなんかダムになりかけてますね。
Ah, it's amazing, amazing... this venue is almost becoming a dam, right?
ありがとう！みんなもちゃんと水分補給してね。
Thank you! Everyone make sure to stay hydrated too.
というわけで、まあ、今日なんですけど、まあ配信イベントということで、
So, today, since this is a streaming event,
みんなはどこで見てますか？
where are you all watching from?
どこで楽しんでくれてますか？
Where are you enjoying it from?
みんなどこで見てるのかな。
I wonder where everyone is watching from.
まあね、あの、
Well, you know,
さすがにね、あの、すごいなんか、
naturally, you wouldn't be watching in a super...
あの、すごいなんか、例えばなんだろう、炎に、炎に囲まれてるとか、なんか滝の下とか、そういう窮屈な、大変な場所ではね、見てないと思うんだけど。
like, surrounded by flames or under a waterfall—
え、トイレで見てるの？大丈夫？！
Wait, you're watching from the toilet?! Are you okay?!
まあ、みんなそれなりにね、あの、それなりの、なんていうんだろう、自分なりのね、ホームで見てると思うんですけど、
Well, I think everyone is watching from their own respective... homes, you know?
まあ、そこで見てくれているなら、そこは会場です！
So, if you're watching from somewhere, that place is a venue!
思いっきりね、くいなく今日は楽しんでいってください！みやも楽しみます！
Please enjoy today to your heart's content without holding back! I'm looking forward to it too!
ということで、まだねみやは2曲しか歌ってないので、
So, since I only have two songs left to sing,
まだまだまだまだ続きます！
we're going to keep going, more and more, more and more!
ついてこれてますか？
Are you able to keep up?
大丈夫？疲れてない？
Are you okay? Are you tired?
オッケー！
Okay!
それでは次も飛ばしていきますよ、
Well then, I'll keep leading you into the next one, so
聴いてください。
please listen to it.
夢の扉！
"Door of Dreams"!
行くよ！
Here we go!
星降る綺麗な夜にはいつも
I always wonder, on nights like today,
考えてみるんだ
thinking about...
心疼る自分だけの未来を
my own future, hidden deep in my heart.
そして
And then,
まだ見ぬきらめく世界に瞳閉じて
closing my eyes in a still glittering world,
想いを走らせてみる
I let my feelings race.
躊躇なんてしないよ
There's no hesitation,
明日を求め続け行こう
chasing my dreams,
何度も挑戦だ明日の鍵を探すたび
searching for that elusive key time and time again.
夢の扉開いた先には
The door of dreams opens wide,
何があるんだ
what awaits me?
ワクワクがほら止まらないんだよさあ行こうか
My heart is pounding, I can't stop! Let's go!
夢の扉 光の誘いへ
The door of dreams beckons me further,
進んでゆけ
moving forward.
道のりは遠く険しいさ ほら
The journey has only just begun—look,
そこに舞いゆわん
there's a new world!
長い夜空は見上げて
Looking up at the starry night,
願ってみるんだ
hoping and wishing,
心からし合わせな未来を
paving a future where our hearts align.
道に迷い一緒な時には
Even on lonely times,
流れ星を道しるべにしよう
let's make the shooting stars our milestones.
ジモンジ特クリ返し答えを求めて
Seeking our own answers over and over.
街中が眠りにつく頃 お前と走り抜けた
When the town falls asleep, running through with you,
星空のメインストリート
on the starry main street.
のら犬みたいに行き場もないのに 遥か彼方 遠くを見つめていた
Like stray dogs with nowhere to go, gazing far into the distance.
月の光のスポットライトで さぁさやかな俺達のステージが始まるぜ
In the moonlight's spotlight, our modest stage is about to begin.
流星のような時間に飛び乗れ ためらわずに さぁ勇気をだせよ
Jump onto time like a shooting star, don't hesitate, come on, find your courage.
明日はチャンスが待ってるぜ ビーツの真似して ハダシで歩いた
Tomorrow awaits a chance; imitating beats, walking barefoot
誰もいない公園通りのストリート
on the deserted park street.
世界中が回っている気がしていた いつか必ず掴んでみたいぜ
It felt like the whole world was spinning; someday I want to surely grasp
俺達の時代を リアルに感じれるまで
our era, until I can feel it for real.
流星のように 今をかけ抜けろ あきらめずに さぁ自分を信じて
Run through the present like a shooting star, without giving up, believe in yourself.
明日はチャンスが待ってるぜ この寒いコンクリートの上で
Tomorrow awaits a chance, upon this cold concrete.
俺達は砂漠をさまようように はてしない夢を追い続けるどこまでも
Like wandering through a desert, we keep chasing endless dreams anywhere.
自由をしばる 地図はいらない
We don't need a map that binds our freedom.
流星のような時間に飛び乗れ ためらわずに さぁ勇気をだせよ
Jump onto time like a shooting star, don't hesitate, come on, find your courage.
流星のように 今をかけ抜けろ あきらめずに さぁ自分を信じて 明日はチャンスが待ってるぜ
Run through the present like a shooting star, without giving up, believe in yourself, tomorrow a chance awaits.
星空のglitter
Starry sky's glitter
あぁ、思い焦がれる
Ah, yearning deeply,
ガラス窓には冷たい雨
cold rain falls on the glass window.
あぁ、こんな夜は…
Ah, on a night like this...
不思議な魔法を願うんだ
I wish for a mysterious magic.
見上げた夜の空
The night sky I looked up at,
君の声を星に混ぜて 掴めたら
if I could mix your voice with the stars and grasp it—
きらめいた星 shooting star shooting star
glittering stars, shooting star, shooting star,
届きそうだな あふれた涙 こぼれて星になる
it feels like it's reaching, overflowing tears spill and become stars.
遠く離れてても 星が降る夜に ほら 僕ら出会えたから
Even if we're far apart, on a night when stars fall, see, because we met.
隣のキミが笑っていたら
If you by my side are smiling,
埋め尽くした涙星は 全部 星空のglitterだ
all those tear-filled stars are the starry sky's glitter.
たった一つだけ 伝えたいことがあるとして
Supposing there is just one thing I want to tell you,
あぁ、そんな時に 使える魔法があるんだ
ah, at times like that, there is a magic we can use.
見上げた夜の闇
The darkness of the night I looked up at,
僕の声を星に混ぜて 繋げたら
if I could mix my voice with the stars and connect it—
きらめいた星 shooting star shooting star
glittering stars, shooting star, shooting star,
届きそうだな あふれた涙 こぼれて星になる
it feels like it's reaching, overflowing tears spill and become stars.
遠く離れてても 星が降る夜に ほら 僕ら出会えたから
Even if we're far apart, on a night when stars fall, see, because we met.
隣のキミが笑っていたら
If you by my side are smiling,
埋め尽くした涙星は 全部 僕たちのglitterだ
all those tear-filled stars are all of our glitter.
星が降る夜に ほら 僕ら出会えたから
In the night when stars fall, look, because we met,
溢れ出す気持ち 届いて欲しいんだ
I want my overflowing feelings to reach you.
遠く離れても
Even if we're far apart,
星が降る夜に ほら 僕ら出会えたから
in the night when stars fall, look, because we met,
隣のキミが笑っていられたら
if you by my side can keep smiling.
埋め尽くした涙星は 全部星空のglitterだ
The stars of tears filling the sky are all starlight's glitter.
閉ざした世界 かすかに聞こえる音
In a closed-off world, a faint sound is heard,
世界で二人 キミみたいだ
just like the two of us in this world.
凍りそうなって すれ違った心が
Hearts that almost froze and passed each other by
ちょっと痛むんだ
hurt a little.
ここで待って ここで待って ここで待って
Wait here, wait here, wait here...
切れられない今まで
Up until now, when we couldn't cut ties,
戸惑いあふれてしまうよ
bewilderment just overflows.
もう何度も繰り返した
We've repeated this so many times,
こぼれた思い出を数えて
counting the spilled memories.
何度も繰り返した
We've repeated this so many times,
世界 世界 金木犀を待っている
this world, this world, waiting for osmanthus flowers.
壊れた世界 傍ばり続ける針は
In a broken world, the needle keeping time
ちぎれた意識 つないでいく
connects our torn consciousness.
歪んだ金属音 鳴り響く心に
The distorted metallic sound echoes in my heart,
ちょっと痛んでいくんだ
hurting a little bit.
ここで待って ここで待って ここで待って
Wait here, wait here, wait here...
記憶繋げないまま
Without being able to connect our memories,
狂って壊れてしまうよ
we'll go crazy and break down.
もう何度も繰り返した
We've repeated this so many times,
神様に願いをかけて
offering a prayer to God.
何度も繰り返した 世界 世界 金木犀を待っている
We've repeated this so many times, this world, this world, waiting for osmanthus flowers.
世界は目映過ぎて この目は耐えられず
The world was much too bright, I couldn't handle it,
傷なんていらないから
because I don't need any wounds.
こぼれた想いは幻
Spilled feelings are an illusion.
もう何度も繰り返した
We've repeated this so many times,
世界 世界 金木犀を待っている
this world, this world, waiting for osmanthus flowers.
もう何度も繰り返した
We've repeated this so many times,
神様に願いをかけて
offering a prayer to God.
何度も繰り返した 世界 世界 金木犀を待っている
We've repeated this so many times, this world, this world, waiting for osmanthus flowers.
開くのを待っている 片翼のキミが待っているよ
Waiting for it to open, the one-winged you is waiting.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最初に お水を飲ませてください。
First of all, please let me have some water.
むせちゃった！
I choked on it!
I choked!
はい、えーと 夢の扉 星空のグリッター
Yes, um... The door of dreams, starlight's glitter...
そして AZKi ちゃんのね オリジナル曲
And AZKi's original song...
「I can't control myself」をカバーさせていただきました。
I got to cover "I can't control myself."
と このね AZKi ちゃんの曲なんですけど、
And, well, about this song by AZKi...
メアは実はカバーさせていただいておりまして、
Mai actually got to cover it, you see,
2年前、
about two years ago,
2年前ぐらいに AZKi ちゃん とコラボでね、 コラボ歌ってみたを投稿したときに、
when I posted a collaboration cover with AZKi,
と当日、 当日にメアもこのね AZKi ちゃんの曲のカバーをアップして、
on the very day, Mai also uploaded her cover of AZKi's song,
なんかそのときは、 なんだろう、 「わあ、 やったー！」 みたいな、 「あ、 AZKi ちゃん と歌えるんだ、 嬉しい」 って、 あのメア AZKi ちゃん本当に神様として尊敬していて、
and at that time, I was like, "Wow, I did it!" like, "Ah, I get to sing with AZKi, I'm so happy." You know, Mai truly respects AZKi like a goddess,
だからなんかそういう、 そんなね、 そんな存在の AZKi ちゃん と今日こうして台湾ライブをできて、 本当に嬉しいです。 え、 こんなね素敵な場に呼んでいただき、 え、 ありがとうございます。
so having such an existence like AZKi, and being able to hold this Taiwan live together today, I'm truly happy. And thank you so much for inviting me to such a wonderful place.
そして今日見てくれたみんな、 一緒に楽しんでくれてるみんなも本当にありがとうございます。
And thank you so much to everyone who watched today, and everyone enjoying it together with us.
ええと、 まあさっきも言ったんですけれど、 今日はね、 こう会場とかじゃなくて、 配信でのイベントということで、
Um, well, as I said earlier, today, rather than a venue or something, it's an event via streaming,
まあ、 こういうなんだろう、 世の中になってから、 なんだろうな、 なんかこう自分のなかで結構その届ける、 誰かに届けるっていうことに関してすごくたくさん考えたここね、 1年ちょっとでした。
so, um, since the world became like this, I've thought a lot about delivering things to someone, during this past year and a bit.
ええと、 まあ、 どう、 なんか新しいことをなんか初めてみたりとかもしたんですけど、 やっぱりね、 自分には歌しかないって思ったし、
Um, well, I tried starting various new things, but I realized that singing is all I have,
そういう意味で、 なんかね、 いろいろね、 あの自分の、 自分の好きなものとか自分のやりたいこととかを再確認した 1年でもありました。
and in that sense, it was also a year where I reconfirmed various things, like my favorite things and what I want to do.
まあね、 世の中きにはなんかこう、 なんか、 ピエン っていう感じなんですけど、 まあ悪いことばっかりじゃないよっていうのをね、 こうして実際にメアがステージに立つことでみんなに届けられたらなって思います。
Well, you know, sort of like "pien" in the world right now, but I hope that by Mai actually standing on stage, I can convey that it's not all bad things.
え、 次でメアのパート、 最後の曲になるんですけど、
Um, next will be Mai's part, and the final song,
次の曲はメアが、 メア自身が作詞をさせていただいた曲です。 みんなへ届けたい想いを書いた曲です。
the next song is a song for which I wrote the lyrics myself. It's a song written with feelings I want to deliver to everyone.
しっかり受け取ってくださいね！ オッケー？ ありがとう！
Please receive it properly! Okay? Thank you!
それじゃ、 最後の曲、 あ、 メアパート、 メアソロパート、 最後の曲聴いてください。 「キミとミライ」
Well then, the final song, ah, Mai's part, Mai's solo part, please listen to the final song: "Kimi to Mirai".
ラララ ほら キミと今 シホニ奏でるよ
La la la, look, playing in harmony with you right now,
あの空まで 届け
deliver it up to that sky!
変わり映えのしない日常に飽き飽きしてるその指先、 そんなキミが望んだ世界はきっとここにはない
Tired of our unchanging daily routine, those fingertips—the world you wished for surely isn't here.
妥協して喧嘩ばっか傷だらけでもあの日の笑顔の方を未来に近づけて
Even though we compromised, fought, and got covered in scars, let's bring the smile of that day closer to the future.
やっぱ晴れちゃった涙はキミに合わない、 きっと昨日のミスも笑えたら怖くないよね
After all, cleared away tears don't suit you; surely if we can laugh at yesterday's mistakes, it won't be scary anymore.
飛ばせ 未来へ 飛ばせ いつかの日が見えたステージ 意見そんな気にするじゃん
Send it flying toward the future, send it flying—the stage where we saw that day's dream, why worry so much about what others think?
飛ばせ 未来へ 飛ばせ いつかの日が見えたあこがれ 音に帰って
Send it flying toward the future, send it flying—that longing we saw one day, turning back into sound,
ラララ ほら キミと今 シホニ奏でるよ あの空まで 届け
La la la, look, playing in harmony with you right now, deliver it up to that sky!
抱え込んだモヤモヤのせい ひとりじゃないなんて言葉を信じられない日もあったんだけど分かるよ
Because of the gloom I was holding inside, there were days when I couldn't believe words like "you're not alone," but I understand now.
だって くじけない才能が君にはある
Because you have the talent to never give up,
まだ 夢色に咲くステージが
The stage blooming in dream colors yet
早く観たいな
I want to see it soon!
飛ばせ 明日へ 飛ばせ
Blast off to tomorrow, blast off!
飛ばせ いつもの日も変わらない
Blast off, feelings that never change any day
想いが この胸にあるじゃん！
Are right here in this heart!
飛ばせ 明日へ 飛ばせ
Blast off to tomorrow, blast off!
飛ばせ いつもの日も変わらない
Blast off, feelings that never change any day
気持ちを マイペースに乗せて
Put your feelings on at your own pace
ララナ ほら 君と今しほりに奏でたら
Lalana, hey, if we play together right now,
手を繋いで行こう
Let's hold hands and go!
ずっと 閉じたそのマニュアルには書いてない
It's not written in that manual we kept closed,
ずっと 秘密の基地においてきた
We left it back in our secret base,
譲れないもの 声に出して！
Shout out the things we won't yield on!
飛ばせ 未来へ 飛ばせ
Blast off to the future, blast off!
飛ばせ いつもの日か夢見た
Blast off to the dream we envisioned one day,
ステージ 行けそうな気がするじゃん！
It feels like we can reach the stage!
飛ばせ 未来へ 飛ばせ
Blast off to the future, blast off!
飛ばせ いつもの日か夢見た憧れ
Blast off to the longing we dreamed of one day,
音に変えて ララナ
Turn it into sound, lalana!
ほら 君といましほりに奏でるよ あの空まで届け
Hey, playing right now with you, let it reach up to that sky!
そこにいる君に届け！
Reaching you right there!
ありがとうございました！君と未来でーす！
Thank you very much! It's "Kimi to Mirai!"
えー、最後の曲が終わったということで、あの方をお呼びしたいと思います。みんな、いいですか？
Um, since the final song has finished, I'd like to invite that person up. Everyone, are you ready?
いくよ？ せーの！
Here we go? Ready, go!
あずき先セー――！
AZKi-sensei!
はい、先生なんですか？迷惑なんですけど。
Yes, am I the teacher? You're bothering me.
認めてる！(笑)
You admit it! (laughs)
いやあ、本当に良かった。なんか、あのね、あのね。
Man, that was really great. You know, um...
あのね、あずきのその、あずちゃんの大好きなとこ行っていいですか？ あの、曲間のMCがめっちゃ好き！
Can I say what I love about Azu-chan? Um, I really love your MC between songs!
待って、それ聞いたら次からちょっと意識しちゃう。ちょっと恥ずかしくなっちゃうんだけど。
Wait, if you tell me that, I'll start being conscious of it next time. It makes me a bit embarrassed.
いや、なんかさ、あずちゃんがその歌ってるその勢いのまま、こう、みんなにさ、伝えるさ、この曲間のさ、メッセージ性、みんな良くないですか？みんなわかる？わかるよね？
Well, you know, the way Azu-chan sings with that momentum and conveys messages between songs, isn't it great, everyone? You get it, right? You all know, right?
先生、分かるでしょ？分かるよね？ ここテストに出ますよみたいな。ここテストに出ますね。
Sensei, you get it, right? You know it, right? "This will be on the test" kind of vibe. This will definitely be on the test.
あずちゃんの良いポイント。ありがとうございます！嬉しい！
Azu-chan's good points. Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
いや、本当になんか、あずちゃんの歌聞いてると、なんか、勇気というか、元気というか、なんかすごい明るい気持ちをもらえます。みんなここテストに出ます。
Man, really, listening to Azu-chan's songs gives me courage, energy, and such bright feelings. Everyone, this is on the test.
わかりました。書く書く書く。メモメモメモ。
Understood. Writing it down. Taking notes.
はい、あ、みんなみんな、分かりみが…分かりみが、ありがとうございます。
Yeah, ah, everyone, everyone, the level of understanding... thank you so much.
いや、本当に、なんか元気になるこの、なんだろう、よ、6曲？6曲か？ いやでも対バンって、そのぶつかり合うんだけど、お互いにエネルギーをこう、そうそうそう、ね、与え合ってる、なんというか。
Yeah, really, it gives you energy, these, what is it, six songs? Six songs? But in a joint live, you clash, but you give each other energy like, yeah, exactly, you share it.
アソ、確かに。それは思った。なんか、なんだろう、普段こう1人でライブやってるよりも、あずちゃんがこんなに、こんなに力強く歌っているから、
Ah, right, true. I thought so too. Like, rather than doing a solo live normally, Azu-chan is singing so powerfully,
あずきももっと歌、なんだ、もっと、もっと気合い入れて歌わなきゃ、とか。え、うそ！ めちゃくちゃ感化されておりますけれども。
So I felt like I need to put even more spirit into singing too, or something. Eh, really! I'm totally being inspired by you.
はい、皆さんどうでした？ みんなコメントでぜひぜひ感想などなど。
Yes, how was it everyone? Everyone, please leave your impressions in the comments.
ありがとう。あ、可愛い！赤、青、赤、青！赤青の、みんなハートもね、めっっちゃめちゃ、めっっちゃめちゃいっぱいいっぱい送ってくれて、ありがとう、ありがとう、ありがたかった。
Thank you. Ah, cute! Red, blue, red, blue! Everyone sending so many red and blue hearts, thank you so much, I really appreciate it.
えらい、えらい！あず、えらい、えらい！
Good job, good job! AZKi, good job!
よしよしよしよし。よしよし。あ、すごい！すごいハート！100点100点100点と！
Good, good, good. Ah, amazing! So many hearts! 100 points, 100 points, 100 points!
素晴らしい！いやあ、パワフルでした！お、嬉しい！ありがとう、最高！ 歌声のシナジー、ある、やった！
Wonderful! Man, it was powerful! Oh, I'm glad! Thank you, awesome! Synergy of our singing voices, we did it!
えー、嬉しい、ありがとう！もうこの衣装からね、いや、もうね、テンション上がる、もうスクショタイムも始まってたから。
Ah, I'm so happy, thank you! From this outfit already, man, our tension is rising, screenshot time had already started.
みんな気になってるけど
Everyone's probably curious...
そう、みんな楽しい
Yeah, everyone's having fun!
100点！
100 points!
ありがとう、100点！
Thank you, 100 points!
撮影始まっちゃった！
The recording started!
はい、ということでですね、まあ改めて、今日なんだろう
Right, so, to recap, today...
もうやってきたんですけれども、もうね、もう終盤なので
we've been doing this, but since it's already the end,
改めてちょっと感想とかを
I wanted to ask MaR-chan for
めあちゃんに聞こうかな
her thoughts.
はい！
Yes!
どうでした？
How was it?
どんなところがなんか良かったか
What parts stood out as good?
いや、まずね、もう本当に
Well, first of all, honestly...
楽しかったし、あの、まず伝えたいことがあって、
It was so fun, and first of all, there's something I want to say—
もう本当に、ありがとうございます！
truly, thank you so much!
ええ、こちらこそ本当に、ありがとうございます！
No, truly, thank you so much!
めあちゃんがね、この開催していただかないと、このライブは、ええ、開催されなかったので、
If MaR-chan hadn't organized this, this live concert wouldn't have been held, so...
開催され、開催され
held—held—
今来たばかりぜが、おっおっおっおっ
Oh, I just got here, haha!
いや、本当に、あの、さっきもMCで言ったんだけど、AZKiちゃん本当に歌手として尊敬してて、
Honestly, as I said in the MC earlier, I truly respect AZKi-chan as a singer,
ええ、もうなんかそれを聞いて、なんかちょっとドキッとしちゃったんですけど、
and hearing that made my heart flutter a bit...
なんてよ！
Why are you laughing?!
いや、だから、なんだろう…あ、AZKiちゃんだ、と思って見ていたAZKiちゃんとこういう風に対バンっていう形でね、あの共演することができて、
So, I'm like... "Ah, it's AZKi-chan!" watching you, and being able to co-star in a joint live format like this,
本当に、なんか、自分にとってものすごく貴重な機会にもなったし、
has truly been such a precious opportunity for me,
いろんなものを学びました。
and I've learned so many things.
いや本当に、AZKiちゃんでも本当にちゃんからたくさん、
Truly, from AZKi-chan as well, I've learned
いろんなことを学んでおります。
so many things.
いやでも、なんだろう、お互いその客の活動はね、もう結構2年、3年とかね、
But you know, we've both been doing activities for about 2, 3 years,
ええっと、やってきてVシンガーとして、そう、やってきて、
doing it as V-singers, and coming this far,
なんかこう、いろんな、さあ、いろんなことがあったじゃん。
and you know, all kinds of things happened.
考え深い。
So profound.
いろんなことが、たぶん活動してる中でさ、楽しいことばっかりじゃなかっただろうし、
I'm sure in the course of our activities, it wasn't all fun times—
これ泣くやつですか？
Is this the crying kind?
なんかこう、そう、なんか、こうやってね、こうやって今2人がここにステージに立っててっていうことは、本当にそれだけで、なんかもう奇跡だなあと、思っていて、
So, just the fact that the two of us are standing here on stage right now feels like a complete miracle, and I've been thinking that...
なんかこうやってずっと活動を続けてなかったら、ここに二人立っていなかったし、そういう意味で、なんかすごく、なんかすごく…いろんなものが重なって、いろんな思いが乗っかって、今日ができたっていう感じの、
if we hadn't kept going with our activities, we wouldn't be standing here together, and in that sense, so many things overlapped, so many feelings came together to make today happen.
そう、なんか、1つ、あの、そう、あの、今年か、今年さ、AZKiもこうやって新衣装になって、そう、で、めあちゃんもさ、その本当に近い日付けでね、
And also, AZKi got a new costume this year, and MaR-chan also got hers around the exact same time—
近い日付けでこの、新、新、しかも、なんか、いい感じの！そう、いい感じの！この示し合わせたかのような、
yeah, with dates so close, and both new, and with such great vibes! It was like we planned it out!
本当に！本当にこれ二人なんですけど、なんかそうやっていろいろお互い活動してきて、こうやって今日2人がここで、ここでこうやって立てているのをみんなが、こうやって見てくれて、来てくれて、コメントしてくれて、本当に
Truly! It's just the two of us, but having done our activities and now standing here today, seeing everyone watching us, coming, and commenting... truly,
なんか、幸せな一日だったなあと、思う。
I feel like it's been such a happy day.
本当に特別な一日をみんなで作ったっていう感じで、いやめあちゃんありがとう！
It feels like we all created this special day together. Thank you, MaR-chan!
ありがとう！ありがとう！本当ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you so much!
本当に、本当に、今日は皆さん、最後、最後じゃないけど、まだあるんですけど、まだあるんだけど、いや、本当に皆さんお越しいただいて、ありがとうございました！
Truly, thank you everyone for coming today—well, it's not quite the end yet, there's still more, but thank you so much for coming!
ぜひぜひLVS3で感想とかもね、ぜひみんなね、もう見に行きますからね、めっっちゃ。
Please, everyone, be sure to check out LVS3 and share your thoughts—we'll definitely go check them all out!
そう、もうあの、終わった瞬間に衣装を脱いで、またお風呂にさっしに行きますんで、ぜひぜひ感想とかもつぶやいてくれると嬉しいです！
Yeah, the moment it ends, I'm taking off my costume and rushing off to take a bath, so we'd be so happy if you tweeted your thoughts!
はい、ということで、ちょっとここで告知タイム！
Alright, so, time for some announcements here!
ええと、一昨日と昨日と開催されました、え、フカカイ2、Qハウ、え、リリディング、形を失った世界で僕らはと、フカカイ2のQ2リリディング世界は分岐するの、え、アーカイブがですね、6月20日まで発売中です！
Um, the archives for "Fukakai 2: QW/W" and "Fukakai 2: Q2 Re:Living" which were held the day before yesterday and yesterday, are on sale until June 20th!
あずき、なんとQ1にでさせていただきました！見たよ！ありがとう！
AZKi, I actually appeared in Q1! I saw it! Thank you!
なんか、やっぱり人の夢がかなった瞬間を見 るって、いいなって、本当に、本当に、なんか
You know, seeing the moment someone's dream comes true is just so wonderful... truly,
夢だったのかなっていう、そう、今までにもちょっと、そわそわしてるんですけど、終わってからも。
was it a dream? Even after it ended, I've still been all jittery.
なんだけど、なんかそう、そういうことがあって、みんなにもね観測してもらって、いや本当に
But you know, having that happen, and having everyone observe it too, truly...
なんか夢を、みんなが、なんか自分がこう、こうなっていたものが
everyone making their dreams come true...
じゃあ、すいません、あの本当に、告知タイムで すいません。
Alright, sorry, sorry about the announcement time!
えと、AZKi先生のモノマネをしまーす！
Um, I'm going to imitate AZKi-sensei!
カメラが…めあちゃん！めあちゃん！じゃあちょっとあとよろしく…！
The camera... MaR-chan! MaR-chan! Um, I'll leave the rest to you...!
床のポーズを床に座らせっていう
Making us do the floor pose and sit on the floor...
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
いや、ずっとやりたかったんですよ、ここで。やりたかった!
Yeah, I've always wanted to do it here. I wanted to!
そう、ここね、そう、このステージでね、ちょっと床になった出来事からですね、え、そこから、なんとか一昨日ライブを、あのゲスト出演させていただきました。
Right, right here on this stage, starting from that incident where we ended up on the floor... from there, somehow the day before yesterday, we were able to guest perform live.
こちらの、Fes Fes Vol.2のアーカイブが残三にて、えっと、6月20日までアーカイブ販売中なので
The archives for Fes Fes Vol.2 are available until June 20th, so...
ぜひ見逃したって方は、もうぜひぜひ鑑賞してほしいので、見ていただけると嬉しいです。
If you missed it, we'd love for you to check it out and watch it.
そして、なんと21時から、お、めあちゃんと、お、面会でアフタートークします!
And what's more, starting at 21:00, with Mea-chan, we're having an after-talk meeting!
お、やあ、おしまい、おしまい、という
Yay, gathering, gathering, so...
皆さん、この機会にぜひぜひメンバーシップの方もよろしくお願いいたします! 最速のアフタートークだぜというこで
Everyone, please check out our membership as well on this occasion! It's the fastest after-talk!
かもん、かもん、めあちゃんも来てくれます。
Come on, come on, Mea-chan will come too.
はい、ということで、めあちゃんのお知らせはありますか?
Yes, so, Mea-chan, do you have any announcements?
私は、今ね、ちょっと言えることがまだないんですけど、あの、いろいろ準備中ではあるんですけど
As for me, I don't really have anything I can say right now, but, well, we're in the middle of preparing various things.
あの、これは、皆さん、めあちゃんのYouTubeチャンネル、そしてめあちゃんのTwitterをフォローしてください!
Everyone, please follow Mea-chan's YouTube channel and Twitter!
そう、このね、あの、直に、あの、お知らせされるね。
Right, soon you'll be notified about that.
あの、概要欄に、概要欄に、概要欄に皆さん
Everyone, in the description box, description box, description box...
めあちゃんの、チャンネルとTwitterを書いておりますので、ぜひぜひ登録して、お知らせを、お知らせを待ってください。
We've written Mea-chan's channel and Twitter, so please subscribe and wait for announcements.
お願いします。
Please.
はい、ということで、それでは本当に今日、最後の、最後の、なんか、最後なんだ。
Yes, so, well, today is really the last, last, like, it's the last.
もう、もう一回やろ?ね、もう一回やろ?
Shall we do it one more time? Right, let's do it one more time?
ツーデイズ、ツーデイズ
Two days, two days.
やろっか。うん。じゃあ今日はね、この曲で締めたいと思います。
Let's do it. Yeah. Well today, we'd like to close with this song.
はい、めあちゃんじゃあ二人で、うん、タイトルコールしましょうか。
Yes, Mea-chan, let's do the title call together.
はい!
Yes!
せーの、ステップアップスーパースター!
Ready, go! Step up Super Star!!
step by step!! キラキラ ドキドキ の カケラ を 集めて let's go!
step by step!! Gathering sparkling, pounding fragments, let's go!
風 は 吹い た でしょ まっすぐ 前 を 向いて
The wind blew, didn't it? Looking straight ahead
さあ どこ までも 走れ!
Now, run anywhere!
(オ・オ・オ・オ・オ...) ah
(O-oh-o-o-o...) ah
(star!) いつも 見上げ て た 立ち止まっ た まま で 歩き出せず に ずっと ずっと この まま
(star!) Always looking up, stopped in place, unable to start walking, on and on like this
(start!) 走り 出さ なくちゃ このまま じゃ ヤダ よ
(start!) I've got to start running, I hate being like this
本当 の 声 が 待ってる から
Because my true voice is waiting
はじまり は きっと ね そんな ささい な こと だ よ
The beginning is surely such a trivial thing
「だって」「でも」「だけど」 ここ に 置い ていこう よ
Let's leave "because", "but", and "however" right here
step by step!! キラキラ と ドキドキ 重ね て 大きく なる
step by step!! Sparkling and pounding, layering to grow larger
胸 の トキメキ もう おさえきれ なく て
The pounding in my chest I can no longer hold back
day by day!! キラキラ で ふわふわ 急展開 ありえない
day by day!! Sparkling and fluffy, a sudden plot twist, no way!
all right!! 覚悟 を 決まれ ば
all right!! If you make up your mind
世界 が 光りだす よ さあ どこ までも 走れ!
The world starts to shine, now run anywhere!
(オ・オ・オ・オ・オ...) ah
(O-oh-o-o-o...) ah
(stay!) 変わら ない まま で 泣き虫 な まま で
(stay!) Remaining unchanged, remaining a crybaby
あの 頃 の 声 だきしめて 描きたくなったの 次元も超える願いを
Embracing the voice from back then, wanting to depict wishes that transcend dimensions
のみこんだ言葉 ここに吐き出しちゃおうか
Let's spit out the swallowed words right here
step by step!! キラキラ と ドキドキ 集め て 大きく なる
step by step!! Sparkling and pounding, gathering to grow larger
ワクワク の ステージ で 今 走りだし て
Now start running on the exciting stage
day by day!! キラキラ で ふわふわ 絶好調 を あげ たい oh yeah!!
day by day!! Sparkling and fluffy, I want to raise my peak condition oh yeah!!
迷い は ない よ ね ? これから 目指す 場所 は ? さあ どこ までも 走れ!
There's no hesitation, right? Where are we heading from now? Now, run anywhere!
世界 で いちばん ? かわいい!
The cutest in the world?
銀河 で いちばん ? かわいい!
The cutest in the galaxy?
宇宙 で いちばん ? かわいい!
The cutest in the universe?
わたくし は みんな の お姫さま ♪
I am everyone's princess ♪
世界 で いちばん ? だいすき!
Loving you most in the world?
銀河 で いちばん ? だいすき!
Loving you most in the galaxy?
宇宙 で いちばん ? だいすき!
Loving you most in the universe?
みんな の こと が … だいすき!
I love everyone so much...
しくじっ た 朝 も まちがえ て 泣い た 夜 も 全部 きみ だけ の もの だ ☆ 愛し ていこう よ!
Even mornings we messed up, even nights we cried and made mistakes, it's all uniquely yours ☆ Let's love it!
step by step!! キラキラ と ドキドキ 重ね て 大きく なる
step by step!! Sparkling and pounding, layering to grow larger
胸 の トキメキ もう おさえきれ なく て
The pounding in my chest I can no longer hold back
day by day!! キラキラ で ふわふわ 絶好調 を あげ たい oh yeah!!
day by day!! Sparkling and fluffy, I want to raise my peak condition oh yeah!!
迷い は ない よ ね ? これから 目指す 場所 は ? さあ どこ までも 走れ!
There's no hesitation, right? Where are we heading from now? Now, run anywhere!
世界 で いちばん ? かわいい!
The cutest in the world?
銀河 で いちばん ? かわいい!
The cutest in the galaxy?
宇宙 で いちばん ? かわいい!
The cutest in the universe?
あづき は みんな の スーパースター!
AZKi is everyone's superstar!
世界 で いちばん ? だいすき!
Loving you most in the world?
銀河 で いちばん ? だいすき!
Loving you most in the galaxy?
宇宙 で いちばん ? だいすき!
Loving you most in the universe?
みんな の こと が だいすき! 今日 は 本当 に ありがとう!
I love everyone so much! Thank you so much today!
しくじっ た 朝 も まちがえ て 泣い た 夜 も 全部 きみ だけ の もの だ 愛し ていこう
Even mornings we messed up, even nights we cried, it's all uniquely yours, let's love it
ステップ・ステップ キラキラ ドキドキ 重ねて大きくなる
Step by step, sparkling, pounding, piling up and growing bigger
胸のときめきも 抑えきれなくて
My heart's excitement cannot be contained
Day by day キラキラ フワフワ 急展開ありえない
Day by day, sparkling, fluffy, an unexpected turn is impossible
Alright 角度を決めるよ
Alright, I'll decide the angle
前だけを見つめればほら
If you just look straight ahead, see?
輝いて色鮮やかに
It shines vividly and colorfully
世界が光り出すよ さあどこまでも走れ
The world starts to shine, now run anywhere!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ピンポンパンポン！
Ding-dong-dang-dong!
本日は LAST V STANDING vol.3 をご覧いただきありがとうございました！
Thank you very much for watching LAST V STANDING vol.3 today!
是非感想を #LVS3 で呟いてください！
Please tweet your impressions with #LVS3!
一つ一つ大切に読んでいきます！
We will read every single one of them carefully!
あずきもみおも！はい！ということで、はい！
AZKi too, Mio too! Yes! So, yes!
はい、今日はありがとうございました！
Yes, thank you very much today!
いやーありがとうございました！楽しかったー！
Man, thank you! That was so fun!
いやー、なんかあっという間に終わっちゃった。
Man, it ended in a flash.
ね、早い！
Right, so fast!
早い。
Fast.
はい、ということで、えっと、21時からメンバーシップのアフタートークがございますので、
Yes, so um, starting at 21:00 we have a membership after-talk,
そこでね、思いの丈を… いや、色々しゃべろう！
so we'll share our true feelings there... No, let's talk about all sorts of things!
いっぱい話すことある。 あの、みんなでね、あの語り合いたいと思います。
There's so much to talk about. Um, we want to chat with everyone.
今日はみおちゃん、ありがとうございました！ ありがとう御座いました！
Mio-chan, thank you so much today! Thank you very much!
いや本当に素敵な素敵な1日になりました！
It truly became such a wonderful, wonderful day!
思い出と… 1日終わっちゃったけど、
With memories... and the day has ended,
これ寝たらまた朝に戻れ… あ、そうそうそうそうですね。
if I sleep, will we go back to morning... Ah, right, right, exactly.
はい、ということで、じゃあまたね、どこかで二人と、二人とまた会ってください！会ってください！
Yes, so then, see you again somewhere, please meet us two again! Please meet us!
はい、でわ、それでは、まったねー！
Yes, well then, see you later!
まったねー！
See you later!
AZKi歌枠リレー企画 LAST V STANDiNG vol.3
[AZKi Singing Relay Project: LAST V STANDiNG vol.3]